# **Ben Stolovitz**

ben.stolovitz.com ben@stolovitz.com GitHub | LinkedIn

## **Summary**

College sophomore pursuing degrees in CS and art with experience in accessibility research, computer graphics, and UI/UX design. Presenting accessibility work at CSUN International Technology & Persons with Disabilities Conference in 2015. Currently working with Wash U's CSE department to revamp & TA intro CSE curriculum.

# **Work Experience**

## Georgia Tech Sonification Lab Student Researcher

June 2012 — Present

- Designed novel modular, rule-based screen reader for web content
- Presenting this screen reader at CSUN accessibility conference
- Programmed audio-diven game for visually impaired 4th- and 5th-graders

## Washington University in St. Louis Head TA, CSE 102

Sept 2014 — Present

- Revamping introductory CSE courses with co-dean of department
- Instructing code-skills classes and guide students in assignments

## **Freelance Development**

April 2009 — Present

- Scripting Spotifious, a popular (35k+ views) Spotify controller for Alfred
- Writing Charles, a C++ ray tracer with refraction

## Flash Foto Events Event Photographer

Oct 2011 — Aug 2012

## Skills

#### **Illustration & Animation**

Aug 2010 — Present

- Lead artist & animator for several small video games
- Co-produced short in Maya from storyboard to blocked animation

## A cappella & Music Production

Aug 2001 — Present

- Singing tenor in The Aristocats, WUSTL's all-Disney a cappella
- Producing multitrack recordings with 15k+ views on YouTube

#### **Computer Languages**

• Fluent in PHP, HTML, CSS, C++, & Java; experienced in C#, Ruby, & JS; basic knowledge of Python **Spoken Languages** English; conversational Spanish; basic Hebrew

## Education

# Washington University in St. Louis GPA 3.55

Anticip. Grad. 2017

B.S., major in CS; minors in art & physics